vegweb.com 2007-08-10

# Privacy Policy

VegWeb Privacy Policy 

This Website, VegWeb, [vegweb.com](http://vegweb.com/), is owned and produced by VegWeb.com, Inc. Your privacy is very important at VegWeb. We understand that your health and dietary choices are very personal subjects, and we want you to feel as comfortable as possible visiting our web sites and using the services. We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you will understand clearly both our commitment to you and your privacy, and how we may collect and use information. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check back occasionally. By using the VegWeb.com, Inc. web sites (veggiesunite.com, vegweb.org and vegweb.com), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can use this form to contact us. 

You must be at least 18 years of age in order to participate in any interactives areas of VegWeb. In otherwords, if you are younger than 18, we cannot allow you to use such utilities as VegWeb.com's VegFriends, Chat, Polls, etc.

Information Collected  
I. VegWeb.com Membership  
II. Recipe Submission  
III. Mailing Lists  
IV. Cookies  
V. Log Files and IP addresses  
VI. Polls and Surveys  
Third Party Advertising  
Other Sites  
Correcting/updating Personal Information  
Policy Changes  
Contact us

**Information collected and how it is used**  
VegWeb will use reasonable efforts to prevent the disclosure or use of your personal information. We will not sell, share, or rent your information in any way different from what is disclosed in this statement. VegWeb collects information from you at several different points on our website. This information is used to enhance your experience on VegWeb and as described below. 

TOP

**We collect information in the following areas:**

**I. VegWeb.com Membership**   
VegWeb does not collect your personal identifiable information unless you provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. If you wish to use certain features on vegweb.com, you must first complete an online membership form. Such features are, but not limited to: 

  * Recipe Comments
  * Q & A Discussion Area
  * Grocery List, Meal Planner, Recipe Box
  * Contests and Promotions
  * Member Profiles
  * Chat

**What information will you ask me for?**

When you register for a VegWeb.com Membership, you will be asked for some general identifying information which will enable us to provide you with this individualized service, including a pseudonymous name (nickname) for your profile. We also gather contact information (like your email address). This information is used to provide the services that you have requested, or to contact you about the service on our site for which you have expressed interest. We may contact you from time to time with news. 

Once you have registered, you will be asked for some personal but non-identifying information to complete your VegFriends profile (i.e. religion, hobbies, whether you have dependants, companion animals, etc.), should you opt to display a VegFriend's profile. This information is linked to your personally identifying information, for VegWeb.com's VegFriends Subscribers to see, if you do not opt to hide your email addresss or you fill out the Profile section titled "Contact Information Viewable by VegWeb.com's VegFriends Subscribers". Obviously, if you provide us with a photograph, some of your information may become personally identifiable information. 

**How will this information be used and who has access to it?**

Your non-personally identifying information is used to personalize your experience, allow other members to find you through a search and to compose your personal profile - which is associated with a pseudonymous identity you have created. Other than your VegWeb.com's VegFriends mail box, your contact information is never available to other members or organizations, unless you do not opt to hide your email addresss or you fill out the Profile section titled "Contact Information Viewable by VegWeb.com's VegFriends Subscribers". 

In the event that you decide to become a VegWeb.com's VegFriends Subscriber, you will be asked for your financial information (like credit card number) through PayPal's secured system. You financial information cannot be read by others when you initiate your order through a secured system. You will know you are in secure mode when the tiny padlock icon - located at the bottom of your browser - appears "locked". 

The personally identifiable information we collect from you is used for internet review and to improve the content and functionality of our web server or customize the layout of our pages for each individual member. We will never release your personally identifiable information to an external organization without your prior consent except for the purposes of validating credit information and collecting debts. We may disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by operation of law, which may include, but is not limited to a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on VegWeb.com, Inc. 

**How long do you keep the information I've given you?**

We keep the information you have given us for as long as you are a member on the site or for as long as we are required to do so by law, which ever is longer. 

**Can I change the information I have already given you?**

You can always verify or request the removal of the personally identifiable information we have collected and change your registration information by logging in and selecting "My Account" from the top-right of any VegWeb page. 

**Do you monitor online behavior?**

Our VegFriends members communicate with each other through chat and onsite mail. While we do not, as a rule, moderate or monitor members' private exchanges, we reserve the right to do so if we suspect users of being under 18 or of using our service for the purpose of solicitation or any other violation of our terms of use or Privacy Policy. Member submissions that appear on the public area of the site are moderated and, if necessary, we reserve the right to edit, delete, remove or not use any communication on a public area of the site. 

Members may choose to participate in community polls. The results of these polls are tracked by gender only and do not reveal any personal identifiable information linked to the individual voters. 

**Contests and Promotions**  
You must be a member in order to enter contests and promotions on VegWeb. Participation in these events is completely voluntary and we do not require you to disclose information. Information requested may include contact information (such as your name and shipping address) and demographic information. Your contact information will be used to notify you if you've won and to award prizes. 

**II. Recipe Submission**  
Your personally identifying information may be used for editorial purposes (such as attributing your submitted recipe to you). We may also use this information to contact you should we have any complications with your recipe. 

**III. Mailing Lists**  
VegWeb has several mailing lists hosted by [www.bcentral.com](http://www.bcentral.com/), and they are subject to the privacy policy there.

**IV. Cookies**   
Like most web sites, we use "cookie" technology on our web site. We may place a "cookie" in the browser file of your computer, however the "cookie" contains only your membership username and encrypted password. The "cookie" does not extract any information off your computer. We use the "cookie" to allow you access to use the features on our site which require membership.

If your browser rejects cookies, you may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that you will be limited from accessing the features of our site which require membership.

Some of our business partners also use cookies on our site. See Third Party Advertising

**V. Log Files and IP addresses**  
Each time a VegWeb page is requested from your browser, we log your computer's IP address into our log files. Your computer has been pre-assigned a 12-digit number. This number is the IP address. We use your IP address to analyze trends, administer the site, track your movements on the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. When you use the Q&A, we encrypt your IP address and include it in your post. This is to help prevent spam. Occasionally, we may have to include your unencrypted IP address in your post.

TOP

**VI. Polls and Surveys**  
From time to time our site requests information from you via polls and surveys. This information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Polls and surveys may also be used to determine how you and other users of VegWeb feel about various issues. Participation is completely at your discretion.

TOP

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use Linkshare and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads and to provide broad demographic information for better advertisement targeting. Privacy issues surrounding Linkshare's use of certain non-personally identifiable user information by its technology are discussed in Linkshare's privacy policy, and are the sole responsibility of Linkshare. That policy can be viewed on Linkshare's [Privacy Policy page](http://www.linkshare.com/privacy.html). 

TOP

**Other Sites**   
From time to time we may have links to other websites from our site. We do not control, and therefore cannot be responsible for, the collection, use or disclosure of your information by any such third party site. Please carefully review the privacy policy of any third party site that you go to from our site. 

TOP

**Correction/updating Personal Information:**  
At any time, you may update your VegWeb member information by editing your Member Profile. After you log into VegWeb, click on the "My Account" link near the top-right of the page, and follow the prompts.

In addition, you may notify us if you wish to cease the use of any of your information by sending a message with this form. and we will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request. 

TOP

**Our policies may change.**  
By using our web sites, you consent to the collection and use of your information, as described above, by VegWeb.com, Inc. If we make any changes to our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Any changes to our privacy policy will extend to any and all information we may collect or may have collected, regardless of whether the policy was different at the time the information was collected.

**Please contact us with any questions or comments**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with VegWeb, please contact us by email with this form or use the following address: 

**VegWeb.com, Inc.**  
P.O. Box 1577  
Surprise, AZ 85378  
USA

TOP
